[
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "95_s01_01_CROW_GracelessRequest",
  "Type": "SeasonQuest",
  "DifficultyLevel": 60,
  "Task": "95_s01_01_CROW_GracelessRequest_container",
  "NpcDestinationId": "9501_Grace_s01_02",
  "AchievementId": "95_s01_01",
  "RequiredLevel": 60,
  "SuccessGameEventId": "95_s01_01_CROW_GracelessRequest_success",
  "ItemRewardName": "95_s01_01_Bag",
  "ItemRewardQty": 1,
  "CanBeAbandoned": true,
  "Repeatable": false,
  "Title": "95_s01_01_CROW_GracelessRequest_Title",
  "Description": "95_s01_01_CROW_GracelessRequest_Description",
  "PlayerPrompt": "95_s01_01_CROW_GracelessRequest_Start",
  "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "95_s01_01_CROW_GracelessRequest_Proposal",
  "InProgressResponse": "95_s01_01_CROW_GracelessRequest_Incomplete",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "95_s01_01_CROW_GracelessRequest_Complete"
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "95_s01_03_CROW_BestOfAeternum",
  "Type": "SeasonQuest",
  "DifficultyLevel": 60,
  "Task": "95_s01_03_CROW_BestOfAeternum_container",
  "NpcDestinationId": "9501_Grace_s01_04",
  "AchievementId": "95_s01_03",
  "RequiredAchievementId": "95_s01_01",
  "RequiredLevel": 60,
  "SuccessGameEventId": "95_s01_03_CROW_BestOfAeternum_success",
  "ItemRewardQty": 0,
  "CanBeAbandoned": true,
  "Repeatable": false,
  "Title": "95_s01_03_CROW_BestOfAeternum_Title",
  "Description": "95_s01_03_CROW_BestOfAeternum_Description",
  "PlayerPrompt": "95_s01_03_CROW_BestOfAeternum_Start_alt",
  "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "95_s01_03_CROW_BestOfAeternum_proposal_alt",
  "InProgressResponse": "95_s01_03_CROW_BestOfAeternum_Incomplete",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "95_s01_03_CROW_BestOfAeternum_Complete"
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "95_s01_04_CROW_ZanderTheRed",
  "Type": "SeasonQuest",
  "DifficultyLevel": 60,
  "Task": "95_s01_04_CROW_ZanderTheRed_container",
  "NpcDestinationId": "9502_Zander_s01_01",
  "AchievementId": "95_s01_04",
  "RequiredAchievementId": "95_s01_03",
  "RequiredLevel": 60,
  "SuccessGameEventId": "95_s01_04_CROW_ZanderTheRed_success",
  "ItemRewardName": "95_s01_05_2hWarhammer",
  "ItemRewardQty": 1,
  "CanBeAbandoned": true,
  "Repeatable": false,
  "Title": "95_s01_04_CROW_ZanderTheRed_Title",
  "Description": "95_s01_04_CROW_ZanderTheRed_Description",
  "PlayerPrompt": "95_s01_04_CROW_ZanderTheRed_Start",
  "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "95_s01_04_CROW_ZanderTheRed_Proposal",
  "InProgressResponse": "95_s01_04_CROW_ZanderTheRed_Incomplete",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "95_s01_04_CROW_ZanderTheRed_Complete"
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "95_s01_05_CROW_CanonAndCoin",
  "Type": "SeasonQuest",
  "DifficultyLevel": 60,
  "Task": "95_s01_05_CROW_CanonAndCoin_container",
  "NpcDestinationId": "9501_Grace_s01_05",
  "AchievementId": "95_s01_05",
  "RequiredAchievementId": "95_s01_04",
  "RequiredLevel": 60,
  "SuccessGameEventId": "95_s01_05_CROW_CanonAndCoin_success",
  "ItemRewardName": "DarkMatter",
  "ItemRewardQty": 40,
  "CanBeAbandoned": true,
  "Repeatable": false,
  "Title": "95_s01_05_CROW_CanonAndCoin_Title",
  "Description": "95_s01_05_CROW_CanonAndCoin_Description",
  "PlayerPrompt": "95_s01_05_CROW_CanonAndCoin_Start",
  "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "95_s01_05_CROW_CanonAndCoin_Proposal",
  "InProgressResponse": "95_s01_05_CROW_CanonAndCoin_Incomplete",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "95_s01_05_CROW_CanonAndCoin_Complete"
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "95_s01_X1_EXPD_Empyrean",
  "Type": "Journey",
  "DifficultyLevel": 60,
  "Task": "95_s01_X1_EXPD_Empyrean_container",
  "NpcDestinationId": "9504_Shailyn_S01_01",
  "AchievementId": "95_s01_X1",
  "RequiredLevel": 60,
  "SuccessGameEventId": "95_s01_X1_EXPD_Empyrean_success",
  "ItemRewardName": "95_s01_e03_2hGreatAxe",
  "ItemRewardQty": 1,
  "CanBeAbandoned": true,
  "Repeatable": false,
  "Title": "95_s01_X1_EXPD_Empyrean_Title",
  "Description": "95_s01_X1_EXPD_Empyrean_Description",
  "PlayerPrompt": "95_s01_X1_EXPD_Empyrean_Start",
  "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "95_s01_X1_EXPD_Empyrean_Proposal",
  "InProgressResponse": "95_s01_X1_EXPD_Empyrean_Incomplete",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "95_s01_X1_EXPD_Empyrean_Complete"
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "95_s01_X2_EXPD_EmpyreanRepeat",
  "Type": "Journey",
  "DifficultyLevel": 60,
  "Task": "95_s01_X2_EXPD_EmpyreanRepeat_container",
  "NpcDestinationId": "9517_OtmarWinkler_s01_01",
  "RequiredLevel": 60,
  "SuccessGameEventId": "95_s01_X2_EXPD_EmpyreanRepeat_success",
  "ItemRewardName": "GypsumOrb",
  "ItemRewardQty": 1,
  "CanBeAbandoned": true,
  "Repeatable": true,
  "Title": "95_s01_X2_EXPD_EmpyreanRepeat_Title",
  "Description": "95_s01_X2_EXPD_EmpyreanRepeat_Description",
  "PlayerPrompt": "95_s01_X2_EXPD_EmpyreanRepeat_Start",
  "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "95_s01_X2_EXPD_EmpyreanRepeat_Proposal",
  "InProgressResponse": "95_s01_X2_EXPD_EmpyreanRepeat_Incomplete",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "95_s01_X2_EXPD_EmpyreanRepeat_Complete",
  "ScheduleId": "Daily"
 }
]